{
    "subject": "resource/Platinum_Equity",
    "predicate": "ontology/foundedBy",
    "object": "resource/Tom_Gores",
    "human_readable": "Platinum Equity was founded by Tom Gores.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9115067720413208,
            "question": "Who founded Platinum Equity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8588244318962097,
            "question": "When was Platinum Equity founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6703436970710754,
            "question": "Name one company founded by Tom Gores."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6096971035003662,
            "question": "What is the name of the company that Tom Gores founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5075676441192627,
            "question": "Is Tom Gores known for founding multiple companies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3589196503162384,
            "question": "What industry is Platinum Equity involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3473418951034546,
            "question": "What type of company is Platinum Equity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24461840093135834,
            "question": "Is Tom Gores involved in business ownership?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18315964937210083,
            "question": "Has Tom Gores received any notable awards or recognition?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12598927319049835,
            "question": "What does Tom Gores do for a living?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Platinum Equity was founded by Tom Gores.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6199_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Tom Gores received any notable awards or recognition?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6199_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Tom Gores involved in business ownership?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6199_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of company is Platinum Equity?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6199_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6199_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6199_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6199_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6199_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6199_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6199_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6199_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6199_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6199_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6199_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Platinum Equity was founded by Tom Gores. The documents mention Tom Gores as the founder of Platinum Equity multiple times, with consistent details about his founding of the company in 1995 and his leadership principles driving its strategic development and direction."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents explicitly state that \"Tom Gores founded Platinum Equity in 1995\" in multiple instances, thus supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}